{
    "subject": "resource/Per_Wahl\u00f6\u00f6",
    "predicate": "ontology/nationality",
    "object": "resource/Sweden",
    "human_readable": "Per Wahl\u00f6\u00f6 is from Sweden.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9800845980644226,
            "question": "Is Per Wahl\u00f6\u00f6 Swedish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9397010803222656,
            "question": "Where is Per Wahl\u00f6\u00f6 from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8721364736557007,
            "question": "From which nation does Per Wahl\u00f6\u00f6 originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.866795003414154,
            "question": "In which country was Per Wahl\u00f6\u00f6 born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8608134388923645,
            "question": "Is Sweden Per Wahl\u00f6\u00f6's homeland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8463807106018066,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Per Wahl\u00f6\u00f6's origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8446270823478699,
            "question": "Where does Per Wahl\u00f6\u00f6 hail from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7980343103408813,
            "question": "What nationality is Per Wahl\u00f6\u00f6?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7957977652549744,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Per Wahl\u00f6\u00f6?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6122283339500427,
            "question": "What is Per Wahl\u00f6\u00f6's country of citizenship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Per Wahl\u00f6\u00f6 is from Sweden.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7166_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Per Wahl\u00f6\u00f6?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7166_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Per Wahl\u00f6\u00f6?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7166_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Per Wahl\u00f6\u00f6 hail from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7166_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7166_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7166_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7166_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7166_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7166_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7166_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7166_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7166_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7166_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7166_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that confirms Per Wahl\u00f6\u00f6 was a Swedish author. Multiple sources indicate his birthplace and nationality, supporting the statement that he is from Sweden."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}